Privacy Policy
==============

Read Naturally Privacy Policy
-----------------------------

_Note: This is the privacy policy pertaining to **[ReadNaturally.com](https://www.readnaturally.com/)**. For the Read Live Privacy and Security Policy, Please click **[here](https://www.readnaturally.com/knowledgebase/documents-and-resources/29/391)**._

Read Naturally, Inc. considers the privacy and security of visitors to our web site to be extremely important. We have developed this privacy policy to communicate our commitment that we will keep any information we obtain private and secure. Read Naturally is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in any manner other than that which is disclosed in this policy. Please note that Read Naturally does collect certain information from our users at several different points on our website. If you have any questions about this privacy policy, or other parts to our web site, we can be reached via e-mail at **[info@readnaturally.com](mailto:info@readnaturally.com)**, or you can call us toll-free at 800.788.4085. Read Naturally reserves the right to revise this privacy policy at any time. Changes to this privacy policy will be posted at this location.

###### Personal Information

As noted above, certain areas of our web site may collect personally identifiable information. The information collected usually consists of an individual’s name, address, telephone number, and email address. This information is required only when an individual wishes to pursue a business relationship with Read Naturally such as receiving product information, or purchasing products from our online store. This information is collected, and stored in a secure, password-protected database that Read Naturally keeps separate from its corporate web site. Read Naturally will not disclose this personal information to any unrelated third party except when a third party is helping us pursue the business relationship initiated by the individual when the individual provided the personal information. Personally identifiable information does not include information that is collected anonymously (i.e., without identification of the individual user) or demographic information not connected to an identified individual (See "Non Personal Information" below).

If your personally identifiable information changes, you may correct that information by sending an e-mail message to **[info@readnaturally.com](mailto:info@readnaturally.com)** and putting the word “UPDATE” in the subject line of the message.

In accordance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, we make no effort to secure personal information from children 13 years of age or younger. If we become aware that a child 13 years or younger age has submitted personal information, we will immediately delete that information and not disclose it to any third party, nor will we attempt to use it to further pursue a business relationship.

###### Communication

From time-to-time Read Naturally sends out promotional and informational communications relying on the personal identifiable information it has collected. You will have the option of indicating your desire to receive or not receive this type of communication at the time of your provision of such information to Read Naturally.

###### Non-Personal Information

Current technology allows for tracking of other information originating from a user’s computer, Internet Service Provider, or another originating network component. This information includes a user’s IP address and domain information, as well as ‘cookie’ information.

With regard to IP address and domain information, Read Naturally uses a specialized computer system to record this data when a user visits our site. This information is only used to provide aggregate statistical information to help us keep the site functional and responsive, and to determine overall visitor usage patterns. This information is not utilized to try and identify specific individuals, or track an individual’s navigation through the site.

Our web site does use "cookie" information to help provide an enhanced functional system experience to those visiting the site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. While our site does use cookie information, only specific cookie data elements helpful for our site operation are accessed and utilized. We may use cookie information to determine ways in which our web site can be improved, but no personal identification information is included in such activities, and this information is not shared with any third party. If a user rejects the cookie, the user may still use the site.

###### External Links to Other Web Sites

Users visiting our web site may find links to web sites owned and operated by other organizations. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving to another web site. While we reviewed the linked sites at the time of the posting of the link, and only provide a link if we believe the content of a site might be of interest to visitors to our site, the content of those linked sites is the responsibility of the organization actually owning and/or operating the site. Read Naturally is not responsible for the content of any linked site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of any linked site as its privacy policy may differ from Read Naturally’s.

### Most Recent Blog Posts

by Madeline Waters

by Brandon Quesnel

[Announcing Read Live's First Price Adjustment Since 2017—Lock in Your Current Pricing Now!](https://www.readnaturally.com/about-us/blog/announcing-read-lives-first-price-adjustment-since-2017lock-in-your-current-pricing-now)  
by Madeline Waters
